ILGWU Photographs 5780 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- David Dubinsky (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Graphics (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Labor Conditions of Textile Workers, 1835 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  Framed letter from Charles Cole to William Lovett
- Liberal Party (Box 58, Folder 7)
- [Miscellaneous photographs] (Box 58, Folder 8)
  Includes: General Strike Committee, Montreal Cloak Makers Union, 1916; Third Joint Conference of Textile and Apparel Workers' Unions of Japan-USA, 1981; Union members take advantage of an art class conducted by the Education Department; unlabeled group photos.
- Portraits (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Puck poster, 1882 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Jerry Soalt photos, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  Includes undated photos
- Union Health Center (Box 59, Folder 1)
  lantern slides
- Brazil, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  Photo album documenting solidarity program in Brazil (Rio de Janeiro, Sao Paulo, and Brasilia), August 30 - September 8, 1977
- Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 3)
  Includes: American Liberal Party rally for Roosevelt, Truman, Wagner, October 31, 1944; Class in gymnastics, Workers University, ILGWU, by Jessie Tarbox Beals, 1926; group photo of delegates to ILGWU convention, 1980s; group photo of men in shop, July 1914; Mandolin Orchestra, class of Local 62, L. Paparello, instructor; Franklin D. Roosevelt and group
- David Dubinsky (Box 60, Folder 1)
  Includes: DD with politicians, sculptor Robert Berks, and others; portraits
- David Dubinsky and Lyndon B. Johnson, 1967-1968 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- New York State Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Conventions, 1924-1962 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  Includes: Local 10, 1962; Golden Jubilee, 1950; Committee on Rules and Regulations, Committee on Officers Reports, Boys of 1910, Cleveland Delegation, Committee on Education, Committee on National and International Relations, Resolutions Committee, Pressers' Delegation, Adjustment Committee, 1924
- Miscellaneous (Box 60, Folder 5)
  Includes: unidentified groups, hands at work, child with umbrella
- Sol Chaikin at Democratic National Convention, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Labor Day Parade negatives, Burt Berinsky [folder 1 of 2], 1961 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Labor Day Parade negatives, Burt Berinsky [folder 2 of 2], 1961 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- "With These Hands" opening, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  Photos and negatives, June 15, 1950.
- 32nd Convention [folder 1 of 2], 1965 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  Contact sheets, May 1965
- 32nd Convention [folder 2 of 2], 1965 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- "With These Hands" stills, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Chicago convention [folder 1 of 5], 1953 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Chicago convention [folder 2 of 5], 1953 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Chicago convention [folder 3 of 5], 1953 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Chicago convention [folder 4 of 5], 1953 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Chicago convention [folder 5 of 5], 1953 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Negatives (Box 61, Folder 13)
  #101A-209A
- Negatives of 1965 Convention (Box 61, Folder 14)
  Berinsky #61802/1-61943/30
- Negatives, 1949-1961 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  Includes: "With These Hands" production, 1949; "With These Hands," 1950; "With These Hands," Washington, March 27, 1952 with captions; David Dubinsky and William Green, April 27, 1950; Legal Department; Nadash; Reuter with Ohio State students; David Dubinsky; Judy Bond; Unity; Long Island Labor Day Parade; Canon Flex; Irons; Stein portraits; Italian-American Labor Council; Labor Day Parade, 1961; Local 48 dance, 1961; untitled.
- Fondazione "Anna Kuliscioff" (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Good Will Tour Italy-Israel, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  September-October 1956
- Good Will Tour to Italy, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Convention, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Rome, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- World War II [folder 1 of 3] (Box 62, Folder 6)
  Italy
- World War II [folder 2 of 3] (Box 62, Folder 7)
- World War II [folder 3 of 3] (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 8] (Box 62, Folder 9)
  Includes: many photos of Luigi Antonini, Local 89
- Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 8] (Box 62, Folder 10)
  Includes: Luigi Antonini, Unity House, Local 89
- Miscellaneous [folder 3 of 8] (Box 62, Folder 11)
  Includes: Luigi Antonini; David Dubinsky; Eleanor Roosevelt; Italia Libera Association; Local 89, Columbus Day, 1936; Count Sforza dinner, April 8, 1949; Cooperative for American Remittances to Europe; Frederick Umhey, Luigi Antonini, Lee Thompson Smith, Dawn Stansell, Hon. Vincent Impellitteri, Colonel Walker Wear
- Miscellaneous [folder 4 of 8] (Box 62, Folder 12)
  Includes: strike rally; Luigi Antonini Avenue; Italian-American Labor Council; meeting with President Johnson, 1964; Columbus Day, 1962; Local 89 in Labor Day parade, 1959; President Johnson at ILGWU convention, 1962; Instituto Interprovincial "Filippo Smalldon"; postcards
- Miscellaneous [folder 5 of 8] (Box 62, Folder 13)
  Includes: Luigi Antonini; Local 89; Local 48, 1951; Mondello; Confederazione Italiana Sindacati Lavoratori.
- Miscellaneous [folder 6 of 8] (Box 62, Folder 14)
  Includes: Luigi Antonini, Local 89, ILGWU convention, postcards, etc.
- Miscellaneous [folder 7 of 8] (Box 62, Folder 15)
  Includes: Luigi Antonini; group photos; post cards; Italian Women's Trade Union delegation; Local 155; installation of 1956-1959 administration; Eleanor Roosevelt; Unity House
- Miscellaneous [folder 8 of 8] (Box 62, Folder 16)
  Includes: Luigi Antonini; Local 89
- Group photographs, 1933-1961 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  Includes: Italian-American Labor Council, Local 89, ILGWU conventions, testimonial dinners
- Miscellaneous printed material, 1922-1947 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  Includes: sheet music for "The Spirit of 89," 1951; Libertas, 1922; citations to Local 89, Luigi Antonini, 1944-1947
- Photos by Jerry Soalt (Box 63, Folder 1)
  No date
- Photos by Jerry Soalt, 1964 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Photos by Jerry Soalt, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Photos by Jerry Soalt, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Photos by Jerry Soalt, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Photos by Jerry Soalt, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous photos (Box 64, Folder 3)
  Includes: workers in shops; parades; Louis Stulberg; Local 155 voting, 1968; protesters at Radio City Music Hall; other protests; General Executive Board, 1947-1950; breaking ground; photo of unidentified group; women reading Justice.
- Miscellaneous photos, 1909-1961 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  Includes: reproductions of call for 1911 memorial; poster for 50th anniversary memorial meeting of Triangle Fire; shop scenes; strikers; classes; meetings.
- [Justice graphics and photographs] (Box 65, Folder 1)
  Some material appears to be reproductions of New York Public Library holdings
- Rallies, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  Circa 1973
- Miscellaneous (Box 66, Folder 2)
  Includes: hands cutting fabric; opening of ILGWU Cooperative Houses; General Executive Board, 1962; Dubinsky receiving honorary degree of Doctor of Laws from Bard College, Annandale-on-the-Hudson, New York, June 16, 1951; Dubinsky with group of representatives at Unity House, 1961; JFK at Liberal Party event; Unity House [?]; unlabeled portraits; faade of ILGWU office; Dubinsky with Franklin D. Roosevelt, Pins and Needles program
- Conference of Secretaries and Representatives, American Federation of Labor, 1919 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  Washington, D.C.
- 12th Convention, 1914 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  Cleveland, Ohio
- 23rd Convention, 1937 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  Atlantic City
- 32nd Convention, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  Miami
- Annual New Yeats Eve. Party - Employees of Bestform Foundations, Inc. - Hotel McAlpin, New York - Dec. 31, 1941 (Box 68b, Folder 22)
- Testimonial Luncheon tendered to Isidore Nagler by the Cutters' Union Local 10, I.L.G.W.U. A.F.L. - Hotel Astor - Oct. 22, 1949 (Box 68b, Folder 30)
- Testimonial Dinner to Samuel Perlmutter tendered by the Members of the Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union, Local 10, I.L.G.W.U., 1934 (Box 68b, Folder 29)
  Hotel Commodore - November 10, 1934
- Testimonial Dinner and Dance tendered to William Altman by Local No. 148, I.L.G.W.U. at Mazzini Hall, Union City, N.J. - Nov. 2, 1935 (Box 68b, Folder 28)
- 3rd Annual Dance, Corset and Brassiere Workers Union Local 32, I.L.G.W.U. - Riverside Plaza - April 29, 1938 (Box 68b, Folder 27)
- Town Hall - Jan. 25, 1936 (Box 68b, Folder 26)
- 15th Anniversary Celebration - Corset and Brassiere Workers Union, Local 32 - Manhattan Center - Dec. 8, 1948 (Box 68b, Folder 25)
- Testimonial Luncheon in Honor of Philip Murray, President of the Congress of Industrial Organizations tendered by American Trade Union Council for Histadruth, 1951 (Box 68b, Folder 15)
  Hotel Commodore - Nov. 1, 1951
- First Annual Dance - Corset & Brassiere Workers Union - Local 32, I.L.G.W.U. - Delano Hotel - New York - April 5, 1935 (Box 68b, Folder 23)
- Bon Voyage Dinner tendered to Julius Hochman - Webster Hall - New York - Aug. 14, 1934 (Box 68b, Folder 33)
- Inauguration of the Label for the Undergarment & Negligee Industry - Governor Clinton Hotel - July 23, 1934 (Box 68b, Folder 21)
- Dinner tendered to Fraternal Delegates of Great Britain by International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union - Shelburne Hotel - Atlantic City N.J. - October 10th, 1935 (Box 68b, Folder 20)
- Cloak Makers' Union, I.L.G.W.U. - Joint Installation - Hotel Astor - March 21, 1962 (Box 68b, Folder 19)
- Distribution Dinner of the Refugee Relief Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry of New York, The Waldorf-Astoria - New York City - January 23, 1945 (Box 68b, Folder 18)
- Cloakmakers' Union, I.L.G.W.U., Joint Installation - Hotel Astor - March 21, 1962 (Box 68b, Folder 17)
- Testimonial Dinner in Honor of Morris Bialis, Manager Chicago Joint Board, Vice President, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union on his Sixtieth Birthday, 1957 (Box 68b, Folder 16)
  Jan. 5, 1957 - Hotel Sherman, Chicago, Ill
- 10th Anniversary Dinner - Corset and Brassiere Workers Union Local 32, I.L.G.W.U. - Sherry's - Oct. 28, 1943 (Box 68b, Folder 24)
- 40th Anniversary Convention, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union - Carnegie Hall - May 27-June 8, 1940 (Box 68b, Folder 40)
- Annual Entertainment and Dance - Corset & Brassiere Workers' Union Local 32, I.L.G.W.U. - Manhattan Center - November 25, 1939 (Box 68b, Folder 48)
- Annual Entertainment and Dance - Corset & Brassiere Workers' Union Local 32, I.L.G.W.U. - Manhattan Center - November 25, 1939 (Box 68b, Folder 47)
- Committee for Industrial Organization, C.I.O. - President Hotel, Atlantic City - Oct. 1937 (Box 68b, Folder 46)
- Welcome Delegates - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union - Atlantic City, N.J. - May, 10-18, 1956 (Box 68b, Folder 45)
- 40th Anniversary Convention, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Carnegie Hall - May 27-June 8, 1940 (Box 68b, Folder 44)
- Welcome Delegates - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union - 40th Anniversary Convention - May 27-June 8, 1940 (Box 68b, Folder 43)
- 9th Annual Dinner - Liberal Party of New York State - Hotel Commodore - June 17, 1953 (Box 68b, Folder 31)
- 35th Jubilee Convention of the I.L.G.W.U. - Chicago, Ill. - May 28th, 1934 (Box 68b, Folder 41)
- Dinner given by the Italian-American Labor Council in Honor of General Mark W. Clark - The Biltmore Hotel - October 12, 1945 (Box 68b, Folder 32)
- 40th Anniversary Convention, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union - Madison Square Garden - May 27, 1940 (Box 68b, Folder 39)
- General Executive Board, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union - Term 1930-1932 (Box 68b, Folder 38)
- Testimonial Dinner in Honor of Israel Feinberg - General. Mgr. Joint Board Cloakmakers Union, I.L.G.W.U. - Half Moon Hotel - Aug. 29, 1942 (Box 68b, Folder 37)
- 30th Convention - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union A.F.L. - C.I.O. - Miami Beach, Florida - May 11 to 19, 1959 (Box 68b, Folder 36)
- 28th Convention Banquet, I.L.G.W.U. - May 22, 1953 - Conrad Hilton Hotel - Chicago, Ill. (Box 68b, Folder 35)
- Convention Hall - May 23rd-June 1st, Atlantic, N.J. (Box 68b, Folder 34)
- Annual Entertainment and Dance - Corset & Brassiere Workers' Union Local 32, I.L.G.W.U. - Manhattan Center - November 25, 1939 (Box 68b, Folder 49)
- 21st Biennial Convention - I.L.G.W.U. - Philadelphia, Pa. (Box 68b, Folder 42)
- Conferences (Box 68a, Folder 8)
- Triangle Fire (Box 68a, Folder 2)
- Maritime House (Box 68a, Folder 9)
- Picture of a painting of a miscellaneous woman (Box 68a, Folder 5)
- Group photos - Officers & Staff (Box 68a, Folder 10)
- Daily News, 1958 (Box 68a, Folder 11)
- Immigration (Box 68a, Folder 6)
- Group photos (Box 68a, Folder 12)
- Child labor (Box 68a, Folder 7)
- David Dubinsky (Box 68a, Folder 1)
- Unity House (Box 68a, Folder 13)
- Child Labor (Box 68a, Folder 3)
- ILGWU - Delegates (Box 68a, Folder 14)
- Executive Board - Waterproof Garment Workers - Local 95 (Box 68a, Folder 15)
- Homework (Box 68a, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous (Box 68a, Folder 4)
- Dinner to Convention Delegates of Progressive Group of Joint Council Knitgoods, A.F. of L., 1937 (Box 68b, Folder 3)
  Hotel Woodstock
- Presentation of Charter by President David Dubinsky - Belt Makers Union, Local 40, 1935 (Box 68b, Folder 4)
  I.L.G.W.U. - Feb. 14. 1935
- Founding of Local 351 (Box 68b, Folder 5)
- Testimonial Dinner in Honor of Charles S. Zimmerman, 1947 (Box 68b, Folder 6)
  50th Birthday by Dressmakers Union. Local 22, Dec. 20, 1947
- Victory Dinner & Dance - Tendered to the Employees & Friends of Primrose Foundation, 1946 (Box 68b, Folder 7)
  Hotel McAlpin - Mar. 16, 1946
- Reception and Dinner to Dr. Leo Price, 1942 (Box 68b, Folder 8)
  Hotel Commodore, Nov. 12, 1942
- Luncheon in Honor of David Dubinsky, 1949 (Box 68b, Folder 9)
  In recognition of his 20 Years of Activity as Executive Officer - Apr. 23, 1949
- 50th Anniversary Banquet - Cloak and Suit Operators Union, Local 1, 1936 (Box 68b, Folder 10)
  I.L.G.W.U. - The Manhattan - March 15, 1936
- Testimonial Dinner tendered to David Dubinsky by the Joint Board of Cloak, Skirt, Dress & Reefer Makers Union, 1929 (Box 68b, Folder 11)
  I.L.G.W.U. - Broadway Central Hotel - Oct. 22, 1929
- Reception and Dinner tendered to President David Dubinsky upon his election to the Executive Council of the American Federation of Labor, 1934 (Box 68b, Folder 12)
  Broadway Central Hotel, N.Y. - Sunday, Nov. 4th, 1934
- Mandolin Orchestra, I.L.G.W.U. - Town Hall -- Jan. 25, 1936 (Box 68b, Folder 2)
- Nagler, Isidore, 1955 (Box 68b, Folder 1)
  60th birthday luncheon
- Founders Dinner Leon Blum Colony in Palestine in honor of Mrs. Franklin Delano Roosevelt and his Excellency Count Rene De Saint - Quentin, the French Ambassador, 1938 (Box 68b, Folder 13)
  Hotel Astor - Dec. 6, 1938
- Roosevelt, Franklin D. - Campaign Elections (Box 68b, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous group photos (Box 68c, Folder 14)
- Arrangements Committee - Masquerade Ball Waist & Dress Makers Union - Local #25, Madison Square Garden, 1914 (Box 68c, Folder 13)
- Group photos - Officers (Box 68c, Folder 12)
- First Exec. Board Dressmakers Union, 1922 (Box 68c, Folder 11)
- May Day 1935 Celebration - Local 89, I.L.G.W.U. - Hippodrome, New York (Box 68c, Folder 10)
- Exec. Board of the I.L.G.W.U. - Local No. 82 (Box 68c, Folder 9)
- Johnson, Lyndon B., 1966 (Box 68c, Folder 8)
- General Strike 1916 - Cloak Skirt Makers Union - Hall Com. - Hall Chair & Sec. (Box 68c, Folder 7)
- Group photo (Box 68c, Folder 6)
- Banquet arranged by a group of friends of Local 43. I.L.G.W.U. in Honour of M. Feigelson & J. Freedman on their 60th Birthday - Montreal, Saturday, June 7, 1941 (Box 68c, Folder 5)
- Cloak and Skirt Makers' Union - Joint Board and Officials, 1911 (Box 68c, Folder 4)
- Locals and Joint Boards, 1914 (Box 68c, Folder 3)
- Relief Committee - Cloak Makers' Union. Local No.2, I.L.G.W.U. (Box 68c, Folder 2)
- Unity House (Box 68c, Folder 1)
- Installation - New York Cloak Joint Board - Term 1937 to 1939 - April 14, 1937 (Box 68d, Folder 7)
- Executive Officers - Ladies Waist & Dressmakers Union Local 25, I.L.G.W.U., New York, October, 1915 -- VERY BRITTLE, Partial picture, some of photo is missing (Box 68d, Folder 6)
- Group photo of Local 40 (Box 68d, Folder 5)
- Joint Installation Cloak Joint Board of New York and Affiliated Locals, Joint Council Cloak Out-Of-Town Dept. and Affiliated Locals - New York Hilton - March 27, 1971 (Box 68d, Folder 4)
- Officer's of the Embroiderers Union - Local 66, I.L.G.W.U. (Box 68d, Folder 3)
- Triangle Fire (Box 68d, Folder 2)
- Triangle Fire (Box 68d, Folder 1)
- 13th Biennial Convention of ILGWU, 1916 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  group photo, Philadelphia, October 1916
- ILGWU Mandolin Orchestra, 1937 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  Town Hall, February 6, 1937
- Staff meeting of Cotton Garment Department, ILGWU, 1942 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  Hotel Abbey, New York, September 19, 1942
- Eighth Annual Convention of the ILGWU, June 1-5, 1908, Philadelphia (Box 69, Folder 4)
  Includes caption: Center of second row, facing each other, are: Charles Jacobson, Acting President (left) and John A. Dyche, General Secretary-Treasurer (right). Beside Jacobson is A. Rosenberg, Second Vice President; alongside Dyche is S. Polokoff, Third Vice President
- [ILGWU Special Convention, Baltimore, Maryland] (Box 69, Folder 5)
  [Israel] Feinberg, [Joseph] Breslaw, Shane, [Jacob] Heller
- Staff of Eastern Out of Town Department, ILGWU, 1944 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  April 28, 1944
- Samuel Gompers, President of the American Federation of Labor, addressing strike meeting that started historic uprising of 20,000 shirtwaist makers, 1909 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  Cooper Union Hall, New York City, November 22, 1909; BT-12575, ILGWU-Justice 8-7 1
- P and N fotos (Box 70, Folder 1)
  book of photographs of theater productions, including Pins and Needles
- 30th Anniversary of Presidency, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  Scrapbook for David Dubinsky, June 1962
- Scrapbook - David Dubinsky, Black and white photograph; Text; News clipping (Box 71, Folder 1)
  large bound scrapbook about David Dubinsky
- Golden Jubilee - 1900-1950 / International Convention Ladies Garment Workers Union, convention Hall, Atlantic City: May 23-June 1, Black and white photograph (Box 72, Folder 1)
  approx. 576 photos total -- 2 panoramic photos re-housed in Mapcase 20 - ILGWU Convention Hall, May 23rd-June 1st, 1950 (2 copies, 1 outside, 1 inside)
- Forest Park Hotel - unwrapped and moved to box 120 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  Forest Park, Pennsylvania; three framed hand-colored postcards
- Entrance to Forest Park Hotel - unwrapped and moved to box 120 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  Forest Park, Pennsylvania
- [Forest Park, Pennsylvania?] - unwrapped and moved to box 120 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Photographs 1911-1980, Black and white photograph; Color photograph (Box 76, Folder 1)
  David Dubinsky; Sol Chick Chaikin; Evy Dubrow; Brandeis Univ. Commencement - June 12, 1966, David Dubinsky; General Executive Board, 28th Convention of the ILGWU, May 18 to 26, 1953-Chicago, Ill.; General Executive Board, 31st convention ILGWU, Atlantic City, NJ.-May 23 thru June 1st, 1962; Delegates to AFL Convention, San Francisco, 1947 -- Contents were removed from box 108
- Unity House, 1927-1935; Text (Box 76, Folder 2)
  Gala Feature Programs; Unity Reunion Dance; Unity House display captions; Sheriff's Sale; John Macy at Unity House (announcement); Breakfast menu; "Just-Us" (vol.1, no.7); "The Unity News" (vol., no.49)
- Unity House, 1935-1971; Text; Black and white photograph (Box 76, Folder 3)
  Dedication, Unity House Theatre Program; :Justice" (vol. LIII, no.19); New Theatre and Opera Festival (advertisement); Corner of Veranda, Forest Park Hotel, Forest Park, Pa. (photo)
- Forest Park Hotel, Black and white photograph (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Pine Hill, New York, 1926 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  Unity House, Forest Park, Pennsylvania; part of Unity House display, caption reads: First Unity House at Pine Hill, Ulster County, N.Y. opened 1915. Local 25 women (Dress and Waistmakers Union) organized a summer center where members could spend their vacation in pleasant surroundings at low cost.
- Circle Dance, 1925 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  Part of Unity House display, caption #2 reads: Pine Hill Resort accommodated fifty. By third season Local 25 opened a larger center at Overlook Mountain in Woodstock, NY.
- Children's Evening, 1925 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  ILGWU Unity House, Forest Park, Pennsylvania, July 1925; part of Unity House display, caption #8 reads: Children's performance added another dimension to Unity House entertainment.
- ILGWU Chorus (Box 77, Folder 4)
  Van Camper, August 15, 1926; part of Unity House display, caption #9 reads: For three decades, Pine Grove Theater was a place of good summer entertainment.
- ILGWU Players at Unity House, 1934 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  Part of Unity House display, caption #9 reads: ILGWU Plays in "All for One"
- Symposium: Women in the Labor Movement (Box 77, Folder 6)
  ILGWU Unity House, Forest Park, Pennsylvania, July 8, 1925. Part of Unity House display, caption #9 reads: Lecture Symposium Shows Fannia M. Cohn (seated) and Professor Theresa Wolfson speaking.
- 1934-35 Championship Game (Box 77, Folder 7)
  Unity House, 142 vs 150, June 27, 1935; part of Unity House display, caption #10 reads: Sports and recreational activities were enjoyed by many union members. Women's basketball championship between Locals 142 and 150 [].
- Water sports carnival (Box 77, Folder 8)
  Unity House, Forest Park, Pennsylvania; part of Unity House display, caption #10 reads: Sports and recreational activities were enjoyed by many union members [] Water sports carnival.
- David Dubinsky and James P. Mitchell, 1935 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  David Dubinsky with Secretary of Labor arriving at Unity House by helicopter; part of Unity House display [?], no caption
- Dinner at Unity House (?) (Box 77, Folder 10)
  Includes David Dubinsky and members with placards; part of Unity House display (?), no caption
- Captions for Unity House Display photographs (Box 77, Folder 11)
- [Triangle Waist Company] - unwrapped and moved to box 120, 1911 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  Oversized reproduction of photograph of Triangle Waist Company factory during fire
- [Triangle Waist Company] - unwrapped and moved to box 120, 1911 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  Oversized reproduction of photograph of Triangle Waist Company factory interior after fire
- [Triangle Waist Company] - unwrapped and moved to box 120, 1911 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- "The Worthless Fire Escape and the Death Trap Below It" - unwrapped and moved to box 120, 1911 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  Mounted reproduction of newspaper illustrations with captions, Triangle Shirtwaist Factory
- "Would it not be better to mar the architectural beauty of the city with a few fire escapes?" - unwrapped and moved to box 120, 1911 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  Reproduction of newspaper illustration
- [Reproduction of newspaper columns] - unwrapped and moved to box 120, 1911 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  Columns include: "What will you do? Labor is asked," "Call Benefit in Brooklyn Tonight," "Official Move to Kill Demonstration"; also includes political cartoon referencing Shirt Waist Factory fire victims
- Garment Worker "Rembrandts" (Box 82, Folder 1)
  signed Harry Rubenstein
- China And Russia Get Union Aid (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Books for Servicemen (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Shop Cheers Allied Victory (Box 82, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Canteen (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Pretties On Middies (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Pots and Pans for Democracy (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Muscling In (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Payzydues (Box 82, Folder 9)
- [Payzydues?] (Box 82, Folder 10)
- U.S. Ambassador Winant Dedicates Seaman's Club (Box 82, Folder 11)
- [untitled] (Box 82, Folder 12)
  man in shop; credit line: Burton Berinsky
- Army Drills Brigade (Box 82, Folder 13)
- "Bertha, The Sewing Machine Girl" (Box 82, Folder 14)
  signed Vandamme, N.Y.
- Men Of Sea Find Home Ashore (Box 82, Folder 15)
- From Shops to Footlights (Box 82, Folder 16)